Guide to the Stanford University, Computer Science Department, HCI Group, CS547 Seminar Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Computer Science Department, HCI Group, CS547 seminar videorecordings
1990-2012
SC1217
Stanford University. Computer Science Department.
18 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Collection Contents
- Videorecordings
  - M. Morris, Animatrix, "Practical Interactive Design" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1992-10-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Mobile Pen-Based Computing, Robert Carr, GO Corporation, 1992-10-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - R. Carr, GO, "Mobile Pen-based Computing" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1992-10-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Active Mail --- A Framework for Implementing Groupware, Ehud Shapiro, Weizman Institute, 1992-10-28; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - E. Shapiro, Weizmann, "Active Mail --- A Framework for Implementing Groupware" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1992-10-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Practical Interactive Design, Marney Morris, Animatrix, 1992-10-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Strudel, a Customizable "Electronic Conversation Toolkit", Allan Sheperd, HP Labs, 1992-10-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - A. Sheperd & A. Ishizaki, HP, "Strudel, a customizable "electronic conversation toolkit" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1992-10-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Film Craft in User Interface Design, Chuck, Clanton, Aratar, 1992-11-11; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - C. Clanton, Avatar, "Filmcraft in User Interface Design" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1992-11-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - An Object-Oriented Graphical Interface to an Intelligent Software Design Assistant, Raymone Guindon, Hewlett-Packard, Design Vision, 1992-11-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - R. Guindon, HP, "Design Vision" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1992-11-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Presence at the Interface (orHow do you nkow I'm not a movie and when does it matter?), Michael Naimark, Interval Research, 1992-11-25; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - M. Naimark, Internet, "Presence at the Interface (or How do you know I'm not a movie and when does it matter?)" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1992-11-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Computers are Social Actors: A New Paradigm and Some Surprising Results, Cliff Nass, Stanford Dept. of Communication, 1992-11-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - C. Nass, Stanford Dept. Comm., "Computers Are Social Actors: A New Paradigm and Some Suprising Results" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1992-11-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Media Streams: Interfaces and Representations Media, Marc Davis, MIT Media Lab, 1992-12-2; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - M. Davis, Media Lab, "Media Streams: Interfaces and Representations Media" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1992-12-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - The Whiteboard Metaphor and Liveboard Meeting Support, Tom Moran, Xerox Parc, 1992-12-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - T. Moran, PARC, "Whiteboard Multiplier & Liveboard Meeting Support" (CS547 Winograd 11), 1992-12-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Introduction to the Seminar on Human-Computer Interaction, Terry Wniograd, Stanford and Interval Research, 1992-9-30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - T. Winograd "Introduction to the seminar on human-computer interaction" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1992-9-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Putting "Feel" into "Look and Feel": Interaction with the Sense of Touch, Margaret Minsky, Interval Research, 1993-10-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Margaret Minksy: "Putting "Feel" into "Look and Feel" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1993-10-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Making It Macintosh: Interactive Media, Interpersonal Design, Harry Saddler, 1993-10-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - H. Saddler & L. Alba, Apple & Albert Farris, "Making It Macintosh: Interactive Media, Interpersonal Design" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1993-10-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Information Interactive Design, Nathan Shedroff, vivid, 1993-10-22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - N. Shedroff "Information Interaction Design" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1993-10-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - From Virtual Reality to Real Virtualities: Designing the Worlds in which We Live, Terry Winograd, 1993-10-29; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - T. Winograd "From Virtual Reality To Real Virtualities: Designing The Worlds In Which We Live" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1993-10-29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Andrew User Interface System as a Multiparadigm Environment for Visual Languages, Wilfred Hansen, Carnegie Mellon, 1993-10-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Wilfred Hansen, CMU "Andrew User Interface System as a multiparadigm environment for visual languages" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1993-10-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Placeholder: Landscape and Narrative in a Virtual Environment, Rachel Strickland, Interval Research, 1993-11-19; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - B. Laurel, R. Tow, R. Strickland: "Placeholder: Landscape and narrative in a virtual environment" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1993-11-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - B. Laurel... Interval "Placeholder: Landscape and narrative in a virtual environment" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1993-11-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Placeholder SRI (CS547 Winograd), 1993-1-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Unistrokes: Pen Computing for Experts, David Goldberg, Xerox PARC, 1993-11-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - D. Goldberg, PARC "Unistrokes: Pen computing for experts" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1993-11-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - David Goldberg, PARC "Unistrokes: Pen computing for experts" (CS547 Winograd 6) remake, 1993-11-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Natural Language in Multimodal Interfaces, Phil Cohen, SRI, 1993-1-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Casual Multimedia: The Use of Imagery in Everyday Activities, Kristina Hooper Woolsey, 1993-1-20; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - K. Hooper Woolsey, Apple, "Casual multimedia: The use of imagery in everyday activities" (CS547 Winograd), 1993-1-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Information Visualization Using 3D Interactive Animation, Winter, George Robertson, Xerox PARC, 1993-12-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - G. Robertson, "Information visualization using 3d interactive animation, Winter" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1993-12-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - G. Robertson, PARC, "Information visualization using 3d interactive animation, Winter" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1993-12-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Animated Programs, Ken Kahn, Stanford CSLI, 1993-12-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ken Kahn, PARC & CSC, Toon Talk (CS547 Winograd 9), 1993-12-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Ken Kahn: Toon Talk (CS547 Winograd 9), 1993-12-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Visual Psychophysics in Humans and Non-humans, with Some Notes on Applications to Computer Scanning, Printing and Video, Rob Tow, Interval Research, 1993-1-27; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - R. Tow, "Visual Psychophysics in Humans and Non-Humans, With Some Notes on Applications to Computer Scanning, Printing and Video"(CS547 Winograd), 1993-1-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - The Information Grid: A Framework for Information Retrieval and Retrieval-centered Application, Ramana Rao, Xerox PARC, 1993-1-6; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Rahmana Rao PARC (CS547 Winograd), 1993-1-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - R. Rao, PARC, "The Information Grid: A Framework for Information Retrieval and Retrieval-Centered Application" (CS547 Winograd), 1993-1-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Towards Conversational Computers, Kai-Fu Lee, Innovation Works, 1993-2-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Kai-Fu Lee, Apple, "Towards Conversational Computers" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1993-2-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Real World User Interface Design - A View from the Trenches, Bob Glass, SUN, 1993-2-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Bob Glass, Sun, "Real world user interface design - a view from the trenches" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1993-2-24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Total Access for Disabled Computer Users, Neil Scott, Stanford CAIID, 1993-2-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - N. Scott, Stanford, CAIID, "Total Access for Disabled Computer Users" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1993-2-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Publishing is Crock, Tim Oren, Kaleida, 1993-3-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - T. Oren, Kaleida, "Virtual Markets and Communities... crock" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1993-3-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - T. Winograd, "Interfacing to the Information HIghway" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1993-3-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Design of New Media Interfaces, Joy Mountford, 1993-5-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - T. Selker, IBM, "Trackpoint II: Making a better mouse" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1993-5-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - UNIX Multimedia: Today's Reality, Scott Weiss, 1993-5-26; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - S. Weiss, GAIN, "UNIX Multimedia: Today's Reality" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1993-5-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - (CS547 Winograd 3), 1994-10-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - High Resolution Virtual Reality, Michael Deering, SUN, 1994-10-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Michael Deering, SUN, "High resoultion virtual reality" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1994-10-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Interface: Where Should Industry and Academia Meet?, Joy Mountford, Interval Research, 1994-10-27; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Audio System for Technical Research, T.V. Raman, DEC Cambridge Research Labs, 1994-10-28; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - T.V. Raman, DEC Cambridge research Labs, "Audio System for Technical Research" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1994-10-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Joy Mountford, Interval Research, "Interface: where should industry and academia meet?" " (CS547 Winograd 2), 1994-10-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Bonnie Johnson, Interval Research, "Exploring the Future in the Present" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1994-11-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Designing for Mathematical Understanding, Rogers Hall, UC Berkeley, 1994-11-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Rogers Hall, "Designing for mathematical understanding" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1994-11-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Building Virtual Libraries on the Internet, Nick Arnett, Verify, 1994-11-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Nick Arnett, Verity, "Building Virtual Libraries on the Internet" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1994-11-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Interface Agents, Pattie Maes, MIT Media Labs, 1994-1-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - P. Maes, MIT, "Learning Interface Agents" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1994-1-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - P. Maes (CS547 Winograd 2), 1994-1-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Magic Cap, Andy Hertzfeld, General Magic, 1994-1-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Andy Hertzfeld, General Magic, "Magic Cap and Telescript", 1994-1-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - An Academic Discovers the Realities of Design, Don Norman, Apple Computer, 1994-12-2; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Donald Norman, Apple Computer, "An academic discovers the realities of design" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1994-12-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - R. Rumelhart, Stanford Psych, "N.N. Applications to Cursive Handwriting", 1994-1-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - The Magic Lens Interface, Eric Bier, Xerox PARC, 1994-12-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Eric Bier, Xerox Parc, "The Magic Lens Interface" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1994-12-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Algorithm Audiovisualization, Marc Brown, DEC Systems Research Center, 1994-1-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Marc Brown, DEC, "Algorithm Audiovisulaization" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1994-1-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - MMDD: An Open Meta-Testbed for Multimeda Distributed Documents, Sha Xin Wei, Stanford, 1994-2-11; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Sha Xin Wei, Stanford, "mmdd: an open meta-testbed for multimedia distributed documents" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1994-2-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Computing in the Year 2004, Bruce Tognazzini, Sunsoft, 1994-2-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - B. Tognazzini, Sunsoft, "Computing in the year 2004" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1994-2-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - The Art and Technology of Spacemaking, Randal Walser, Spacetime Arts, Inc, 1994-2-25; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - R. Walser, Spacetime, "The Art and Technology of Spacemaking" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1994-2-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Sensemaking: What People do to Understand Their World, Dan Russell, Apple ATG, 1994-2-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - D. Russell, Apple, "Sensemaking: What people do to understand their world" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1994-2-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - D. Russell, Apple ATG, "Sensemaking: What people do to understand their world", 1994-2-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Interfacing to the Information Highway, Terry Winograd, Stanford, 1994-3-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - T. Winograd, "Interfacing the Information History" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1994-3-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Designing for the Consumer, Paul SAffo, Institute for the Future, 1994-4-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Paul Saffo, Institute for the Future, "Designing for the consumer" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1994-4-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Color Science for Computer-Human Interface Designs, Charles Poynton, SUN, 1994-4-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Charles Poynton, Sun, "Color Science for Computer-Human Interface Designs" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1994-4-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - (CS547 Winograd 5), 1994-4-29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Managing Metaphor in Advanced Uls, Aaron Marcus, Aaron Marcus Associates, 1994-5-13; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Aaron Marcus, Aaron Marcus Associates, "Managing Metaphor in Advanced Uls" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1994-5-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Heuristic Evaluation of User Interfaces, Jakob Nielsen, Sunsoft, 1994-5-20; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jakob Nielsen, Sunsoft, "Heuristic Evaluation of User Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1994-5-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Media Streams: Representing Video for Retrieval and Repurposing, Marc Davis, MIT Media Lab and Interval Research, 1994-5-27; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Marc Davis, MIT Media Lab and Interval Research, "Media: Streams: Representing Video for Retrieval and Repurposing" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1994-5-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Proactive and Reactive Agents in User Interface, Ted Selker, IBM, 1994-5-6; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ted Selker, IBM, "Proactive and Reactive Agents in User Interface" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1994-5-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Spreadsheets for Images, Marc Levoy, Stanford Computer Science, 1994-9-30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Marc Levoy, Stanford CS, "Spreadsheets for Images" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1994-9-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Sketching Information, Takeshi Sunaga, Tama Art University, Tokyo, 1995-10-13; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Takeshi Sunaga: Sketching Information (CS547 Winograd 3), 1995-10-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Hypermedia Applications in BETA, Elmer Sandvad, University of Oslo, 1995-10-20; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Nygaard et al: Hypermedia in Beta (CS547 Winograd 4), 1995-10-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - The Wheel of Life, A Transformational Theater Piece, Larry Friedlander, Overeducated Cartoonist, 1995-10-27; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Larry Friedlander: Wheel of Life, Transformational Theatre Piece (CS547 Winograd 5), 1995-10-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Enabling and Constraining Effects of New Technologies, Jonathan Grudin, UC Irvine, 1995-10-6; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jonathan Grudin, UC Irvine, Enabling and Constraining Effects of New Technologies (CS547 Winograd 10), 1995-10-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - The Establishment of Identity in Virtual Communities, Judith Donath, MIT Media Lab, 1995-11-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Judith Donath: Establishment of Identity in Virtual Communities (CS547 Winograd 7), 1995-11-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - New Voices, New Visions, Sally Rosenthal, Interval Research, 1995-11-17; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Sally Rosenthal: New Voices, New Visions (CS547 Winograd 8), 1995-11-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Interacting with the Digital Library, Terry Winograd, Stanford Computer Science, 1995-11-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Winograd: DigLab: Interacting with the Digital Library (CS547 Winograd 6), 1995-11-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Bringing Behavior to the Internet, James Gosling, SUN Microsystems, 1995-12-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Gosling: Java (CS547 Winograd 9), 1995-12-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Information Playgrounds: Local Metaphors for Interactive Information, Eviatar Shafrir, Hewlett-Packard, 1995-1-27; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Eviatar Shafrir, HP, "Infromation Playgrounds: Local Metaphors for Interactive Information" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1995-1-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Universal Design, Betsy Bayha, World Institute on Disability, 1995-12-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Betsy Bayha: Universal Design (CS547 Winograd 10), 1995-12-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - M. King- Ventura (CS547 Winograd 10), 1995-12-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Directed Improvisation by Computer Characters, Barbara Hayes Roth, Stanford Knowledge Systems Lab, 1995-2-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Barbara Hayes Roth, Stanford Knowledge Systems Laboratory, "Directed Improvisation by Computer Characters" (CS547 Winograd 4) Wk# 1209, 1995-2-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Applications of WWW in Education of Engineering Design Teams, Larry Leifer, Stanford Center for Design Research, 1995-9-29; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jack Hong: Web and ME210: Applications of WWW in Education of Engineering Design Teams (CS547 Winograd 1), 1995-9-29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Untangling the Web, Srinjia Srinivasan, Yahoo! Inc, 1996-10-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Srinija Srinivasan, Yahoo! Inc., "Untangling the Web" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1996-10-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Ensuring the Usability of the Next Computing Paradigm, Jakob Nielson, SUN Microsystems, 1996-10-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jakob Nielson, SUN Microsystems, "Ensuring the usability of the next computing paradigm" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1996-10-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Accounting for System Action, Paul Dourish, Apple Research Lab, 1996-11-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Paul Dourish, Apple Research Labs, "Accounting for System Action" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1996-11-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Learning Works, Adele Goldberg, Neometron, 1996-11-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Adele Goldberg, Neometron, "Learning Works" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1996-11-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - The Socialization of Cyberspace: From Habitat to the Full Service Network, Randy Farmer, Electric Communities, 1996-1-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Randy Farmer, Doug Crockford, "The socialization of cyberspace: From habitat to the full service network" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1996-1-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Sketching: Past, Present and Future, John Hughes, Brown University, Computer Graphics Group, 1996-11-22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - John Hughes, Brown Univeristy, Computer Graphics Group, "Sketching: Past, Present and Future" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1996-11-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Performance in 6 Degree-of-Freedom Input Control, Shumin Zhai, IBM Almaden Research Lab, 1996-11-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Shumin Zhai, IBM Almaden Research Laboratory, "Human Performance in 6 Degree-of-Freedom Input Control" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1996-11-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Shumin Zhai, M. King-Ventura (CS547 Winograd), 1996-11-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Social Activity in CSCW Systetms, Mark Ackerman, UC Irvine, 1996-1-19; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Mark Ackerman, UC Irvine, "Social Activity in CSCW Systems" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1996-1-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Multivalent Documents: Documents as Interfaces to Information in Network Digital Repositories, Robert Wilensky, UC Berkeley, 1996-1-26; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Thomas Phelps, UC Berkeley, "Multivalent Documents: Documents as interfaces to Information in network digital repositories" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1996-1-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - VizAbility, Kristina Hooper Woolsey, 1996-2-16; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Gayle Curtis, Scott Kim, Kristina Hooper Woolsey, "VizAbility" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1996-2-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - A Digital Library Interface, Rebecca Lasher, Stanford, 1996-2-2; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Steve Cousins, Rebecca Lasher, Andreas Paepcke, Stanford, "A Digital Library Interface" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1996-2-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Space Craft: Perceptual Aids for Cognitive ACtivity, Kevin Mullet, Macromedia, 1996-2-23; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Kevin Mullet, Macromedia, "Space Craft: Perceptual aids for cognitive activity" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1996-2-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Information Society in a Post-Communist Environment: The Croatian Experience, Enver Sehovic, University of Zagreb, Croatia, 1996-2-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Enver Sehovic, University of Zagreb, Croatia, "Information Society in a Post-Communist Environment: The Croatian Experience" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1996-2-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Design for Interactivity: From Diagrams to Virtual Reality, Yvonne Rogers, University of Sussex, 1996-3-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Yvonne Rogers, University of Sussex, "Design for Interactivity: From diagrams to virtual reality" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1996-3-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Magic Cap, Kevin Lynch, General Magic, 1996-3-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Kevin Lynch, General Magic, "Magic Cap" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1996-3-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Emacspeak, T. V. Raman, Adobe Systems, 1996-3-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - T. V. Raman, Adobe Systems, "Emacspeak" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1996-3-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Interactive Sketching for the Early Stages of User Interface Design, James Landay, Carnegie Mellon University, 1996-4-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - James Landay, Carnegie Mellon University, Interactive Sketching for the Early Stages of User interface Design" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1996-4-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - International User Interface Design, Tony Fernandes, Netscape, 1996-4-19; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Tony Fernandes, Netscape, "International User Interface Design" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1996-4-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Interfacing to Microworlds, Will Wright, Maxis, 1996-4-26; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Will Wright, Maxis, "Interfacing to Mircoworlds" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1996-4-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)